昨晚  我杀了迪伦・辛奇  因为他杀了我女儿
Last night, I killed Dylan Hinchey for killing my little girl.
你没有杀他  肯尼  迪伦・辛奇还活着
You didn't kill him, Kenny. Dylan Hinchey's alive.
《东城梦魇》前情提要
我需要迪伦提供一份DNA样本
I need Dylan to submit a DNA sample.
我们收到消息称他可能不是DJ的亲生父亲
We received information that he might not be DJ's real father.
如果我们上法庭
If we go to court,
我会告诉法官你是个不称职的母亲
I'm gonna tell the judge that you're an unfit mother.
他是我儿子  该死  我的
He's my son, goddammit! Mine!
她才是他妈  她会得到监护权
She's the mother. She'll get custody,
你和我都阻止不了
and there's not a damn thing you or I can do about it.
法医说她的死亡时间在午夜到凌晨两点之间
The ME said she was killed between midnight and 2:00 a.M.
我们现在离克里顿小溪22公里
We're 13.7 miles away from Creedham Creek.
她不可能骑车骑这么远
There's no way she rode her bike that far.
肯定有人来接了她
Someone must have picked her up.
局里接到一个叫凯莉・雷顿的电话
Station got a call from Carrie Layden.
警察在她车上储物箱里找到两袋海洛因
Cops found two packets of heroin in her glove compartment.
她发誓肯定是你栽赃给她的
She swore that you must have planted them on her.
她是瘾君子  她什么都说得出口
She's a drug addict. She'll say anything.
-交出枪和警徽  -拜托
- Gun and badge. - Please...
梅尔
Mare?
梅尔  你  你今晚会回家吗
Mare, are you-- are you gonna be home tonight
还是说你要加班
or are you-- are you working late?
我应该会回家
Uh, yeah, I should be home.
好  那我就做烤鸡
Okay, well, I'll-- I'll roast a chicken then.
德鲁  给外婆道别
Hey, Drew, say-- say goodbye to your grandma.
-拜拜  外婆  -拜拜
- Bye, Gran! - Okay, bye.
拜  妈
Bye, Mom.
东城梦魇
第一季  第四集
拿去
Take 'em.
如果我再要  就叫我滚
If I ask for another one, tell me to fuck off.
你有跟你家人说吗
Did you tell your family yet?
我必须说吗
Do I have to?
我想你也可以
Uh, I mean, I guess you could
假装你每天都去上班
just pretend to go to work every day.
局长让我去见一个悲痛治疗专家
Chief's making me see some grief therapist
作为我停职的一部分
as a part of my suspension.
我知道这不是你想要的  梅尔
Well, I know it's not what you want, Mare,
但暂时退出或许是好事
but it might be a good thing to step away.
还有凯蒂・贝里  艾琳
And Katie Bailey, Erin...
你家人很担心你
Your family's worried about you.
你不再说话了
You're not talking anymore.
你从不谈起他  梅尔
You never talk about him anymore, Mare.
我儿子自杀了  洛尔
Yeah, my son killed himself, Lor.
抱歉如果我不能逗人开心
I'm sorry if I'm not the life of the fucking party.
首先  你从来就不会逗人开心
Well, first of all, you were never the life of the party.
你在疏远所有人
You're pushing everyone away.
包括你吗
Including you?
不  我不会允许你这么做
No, I won't let you.
好了  两份奶油  不加糖
All right. Two creams, no sugar.
早啊  头儿
Morning, Chief.
豪瑟
Hauser.
-你怎么来了  -早  扎博尔  关门
- What are you doing here? - Morning, Zabel. Shut the door.
怎么了  梅尔呢
What's going on? Where's Mare?
她要退出麦克梅纳明的案子
She's stepping back on the McMenamin case,
需要时间处理私事
needs some time to deal with her personal stuff.
接下来你将领头
You'll run point moving forward.
豪瑟警探会协助你
Detective Hauser will assist you.
DNA结果今早出来了
DNA results came in this morning.
弗兰克・希安不是那孩子的父亲
Frank Sheehan isn't that baby's father.
迪伦・辛奇也不是
Neither is Dylan Hinchey.
-总有人是  -废话  小子
- Well, somebody is. - No shit, kid.
如果需要什么  我就在办公室
I'll be in my office if you need anything.
那是给我的吗  高手
That for me, hotshot?
是的
Yeah. Sure.
你有混合奶油吗
You got any half-and-half?
那边就是厨房
There's a kitchen right over there.
-一只耳朵和它的兄弟  -天呐
- "One ear and his brother." - Oh, my gosh.
-一个嘴巴  一个大鼻子  -天呐
- "One mouth, one big nose." - Oh, my gosh.
两只脚有一二三四
"Two feet with one, two, three, four,
五六七八九十根脚趾
five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten toes."
你为什么要那么对他
Why the hell are you treating him like that?
怎么对他
Treat him like what?
亲他  拥抱和大笑
Kissing him, and hugging and laughing.
他根本不是我们家的
He ain't even ours.
这不是他的错  D
It's not his fault, D.
他是个婴儿  我们得照顾他
He's a baby. We gotta take care of him.
带他出去
Get him outta here.
D  你得冷静
D, you gotta stay calm.
-迪伦  别这样  -带他出去
- Dylan, stop. - Get him outta here!
-迪伦  -出去
- Dylan. - Out!
走吧
Come on.
吃蔬菜
Eat your vegetables, please.
我不喜欢西兰花
I don't like broccoli, Granny.
你妈妈喜欢西兰花
Well, your mom loved broccoli.
我以前跟她说她会变成
I used to tell her she was gonna turn into
西兰花  她吃了好多
a piece of broccoli, she ate so much of it.
一大块绿色西兰花
A big green piece of broccoli.
喂
Hello?
你想你女儿吗  道恩
Do you miss your daughter, Dawn?
因为凯蒂很想你  你在听吗
'Cause Katie misses you. Are you listening to me?
你是谁  为什么打给我
Who are you? Why are you calling me?
我打来是告诉你凯蒂准备回家了
I'm calling to tell you Katie's ready to come home.
如果凯蒂在的话  把电话给她
Well, if Katie's there, then put her on the phone.
-不行  道恩  -我不信你
- I can't do that, Dawn. - I don't believe you.
如果凯蒂在你那  证明她还活着
If you have Katie, prove to me that she's alive.
五千块
Five thousand dollars.
我没有五千块  我...
I don't have five thousand dollars. I don't--
-凯蒂需要你  道恩  -等等
- Katie needs you, Dawn. - Oh, wait, wait, wait.
别挂  求你了  拜托  别挂
Don't hang up. Please, please, don't hang up.
-我会再联系你  -喂
- I'll be in touch. - Hello?
喂
Hello?
我们要开个家庭会议
We're having a family meeting.
开个啥
A what?
德鲁  来
Drew. Um, here you go.
外婆的平板电脑
Nana's iPad.
拿着  去我房间玩玩游戏  好吗
Here, take that into my room and, uh, play a game, okay?
去吧  记得把门关上  好了
Okay. And, uh, close the door. All right.
-妈  -怎么了
- Mom? - Yeah?
我们要开个家庭会议
We're having a family meeting.
家庭会议是什么鬼
The hell's a family meeting?
总之  都来客厅开家庭会议  好吗
All right. Family meeting in the dining room, okay?
我从警局的证物柜里偷了两袋海洛因
I stole two bags of heroin from the evidence closet at work
把它们栽赃到了凯莉的车上
and I planted them in Carrie's car.
我希望她能在路上被拦下
I was hoping that she'd get pulled over
然后因为持有毒品而被捕
and arrested for possession.
结果适得其反了
But it backfired, and, um...
头儿知道是我干的  所以我被停职了
Chief, uh, knows it was me, and I've been suspended.
我的天  梅丽安
My God, Marianne.
我不知道该说什么了
I-- I-- I don't know what the hell to say.
等等  我想起来了  太蠢了
Oh, wait. It just came to me. That was stupid!
你他妈脑残吗
Goddamn idiotic!
你是欠抽了吧  居然干出那种事
You're a complete smacked-ass for doing that.
谢了  妈
Thanks, Mom.
凯莉知道是你干的吗
Does Carrie know it was you?
-不  她没法证明  -谢天谢地
- She can't prove it, no. - Well, thank God.
她要是知道  我们就得永远失去德鲁了
Otherwise, we'd lose Drew forever.
你有什么想法吗
Any thoughts?
我觉得外婆总结得很到位了
I think Gran summed it up nicely.
不过如果是要分享生活的话  我今天跟贝卡分手了
But if we're sharing, I split up with Becca today.
你...你有别人了吗
You-- Did you meet somebody else?
没有  就是顺其自然分手了
No. No, it just ran its course.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
你有什么想分享的事吗  妈
Do you have anything you'd like to share, Mom?
你似乎还想说点什么
You seem like you wanna say something else.
没有  只是不知道我他妈要怎么办
No. Just wondering what the hell I'm gonna do,
天天跟你困在一起
stuck in the house with you all day.
格兰姆医生吗
Dr. Graham?
-我是梅尔・希安  -你好
- Mare Sheehan. - Hi.
你肯定见过不少警察吧
So, I bet you see a lot of cops, huh?
对  这些年来确实见过几个
Oh, I've seen a few over the years, yes.
都是硬骨头吧  就好像...他们不想来
Hard cases, right? Like, they don't wanna be here.
他们不觉得自己需要帮助
They don't think they need the help.
-有些是的  不过大部分...  -我只想说
- Oh, some, but most are-- - You know, I just wanna say
在这点上你不用担心我
you don't have to worry about that with me.
我会准时来报道  不缺席
I'll be here on time, every time.
-太好了  -很好
- Wonderful. - Awesome.
其实你来得早了一点
You're actually a little bit early.
这事到底怎么进行
So, how does this work, exactly?
比如  我过来  我们聊开
Like, you know, I come in, we talk it out,
你向局里提交报告说我很合作
you submit a report to the department saying I cooperated,
我们坚持一段时间  然后就能完事了
and we do that for a while and we're good to go?
-基本是的  -好
- Basically, yes. - Okay.
只是...
It's just, um...
在我们开始之前...
you know, before we get into all this...
我希望你别有挫败感  仅此而已
I don't want you to get discouraged. That's all.
挫败感
Discouraged?
就是  如果没有什么重大突破之类的
Like, you know, if there's not, like, a big breakthrough
你懂吗  那不是你的错
or something, you know? It's not you.
我以前也做过这些  心理治疗
I've done this before. Therapy.
我和我丈夫  我们做过婚姻咨询
Me and my husband, we saw this marriage counselor.
那是什么感觉
What was that experience like?
我们最后离婚了
We're divorced.
好吧  这就是我想说的  好吗
Right. So, like, that's what I mean. You know?
我了解这种事
I mean, I understand this kind of thing
对某些人可能会有帮助
can be helpful for some people.
我以前跟一个警察共事过  叫斯威尼  是个混蛋
This cop I used to work with, Sweeney, fucking prick,
他以前...
he, uh, used to, you know,
就是...有一天晚上他出去巡逻
like he-- he-- he was out on patrol one night
开车撞到了一个老太太
and, um, ran his car into an old lady
她死了  你懂吗  把他折腾得不轻
and killed her, you know? Really messed him up.
于是他开始见心理医生
So he started seeing a therapist.
两个月后  他辞职了  买了条狗
Two months later, he, uh, quits his job, buys a dog,
开始...随时都会拥抱他老婆
starts, like, hugging his wife all the time.
现在他在福吉谷当公园导游
And now he's a park guide over at Valley Forge.
幸福得不得了  万岁
Happy as a clam. Bingo.
只是  对我来说  我...
It's just, for me, I, you know...
-还没起过作用  -对
- Hasn't worked yet? - Right.
对  你懂的
Right. You know.
总之  我只是想先说清楚
Anyway, so I just wanna throw that out there.
以免你失望
So you're not, like,
如果没有那种"阿弥陀佛"式的开悟的话
disappointed if there's not a big "Hallelujah" Moment.
明白  我们试试看吧
Understood. Why don't we try?
让治愈开始吧
Let the healing begin.
马克执事  我是扎博尔警探
Deacon Mark, Detective Zabel.
-你好  -你好
- Yes. Hello. - Hi.
过去这几天我一直在联系你
Been trying to get a hold of you for the past few days.
你收到我的语音留言了吗
Did you get my voicemails?
有  收到了  抱歉
Yes. Yes, I did. Sorry. Sorry.
教堂那边有点忙
Things have been busy over at the church.
我都要以为你是在故意躲我了
I was beginning to think you were avoiding me.
你有吗
Were you?
我能怎么帮你  警探
What can I help you with, Detective?
我只是想问问你是在
Well, uh, I just wanted to ask you some questions
什么情况之下调来
about the circumstances
圣迈克尔教堂的
of your transfer here to St. Michael's.
恐怕我帮不上什么忙
Well, I'm afraid I won't be much help.
所有奥古斯丁教团教士的调动安排
All Augustinian reassignments
都是由教区办公室定的  所以...
are dealt with the provincial's office, so--
具体点说吧  我想问问你之前的教区中
Well, more specifically about the sexual misconduct complaint
一位14岁女孩的父母投诉
filed against you at your previous parish
你有不正当性行为的情况
by, uh, the parents of a 14-year-old girl.
大主教管区叫我
Uh, I've been instructed by the archdiocese
不要谈论那次事件
not to speak about that case.
执事  我...  我从小在天主教家庭中长大
Look, Deac, I-- I-- I was raised Catholic.
我在努力站在你这一边
I'm trying to be on your side here.
但你可以理解我为什么对这件事很关注  对吧
But you can understand why I'd be concerned, right?
我发现艾琳・麦克梅纳明
I find out that the last person
遇害当晚和她最后讲过话的人
to speak with Erin McMenamin on the night she's murdered
可能曾与另一位少女
potentially had an inappropriate relationship
有不正当关系
with another young girl.
大主教管区调查过那件事了  警探
The archdiocese investigated the incident, detective,
并确信并未发生什么事  什么都没发生
and believe nothing happened. Nothing.
那我该相信什么呢
And what should I believe?
你最好把你的事说清楚  马克
You better start getting your story straight, Mark.
因为如果有人告诉了我你的历史
'Cause if I got the tip about your past,
要不了多久  大家都会知道的
it won't be long till everyone finds out.
谢谢
Thank you.
我是说...  我的意思是  我花了好久
Well, I mean-- I mean, it took me a long time
才明白这点  但现实就是
to realize this, but the reality is,
我可能不是大作家的料
I, you know, maybe I'm just not a great writer.
我...  只能写出一本书  但是呢
I-- I only had one book in me, you know. But you know what?
我可以坦然接受
I'm okay with that.
至少你还成功过一次
Well, at least you had your one shot.
大多数人连那个成就都没有
Most people never even get that.
你也有过啊  鹰夫人
You got yours, Lady Hawk.
-你喜欢做老师吗  -我...  我开始喜欢了
- You like being a teacher? - Um, well, I've-- I've grown to.
我之前一向把教书看作
Um, I always used to look at teaching
看作是
as the-- the thing that you did
如果你做不来你想做的  就可以去做的那种事
if you couldn't do the thing you wanted to do.
所以这是一种善意的提醒
So it's kind of a nice reminder
提醒我  我的人生在稳步倒退
that my life is steadily declining.
我真幸运  在你走下坡路时遇到了你
Lucky me. Catch you on the down slide, huh?
你和德鲁的妈妈谈过了吗
Hey, did you talk to Drew's mother?
-嗯  谈过了  -结果呢  结果怎么样
- Uh, yeah. Yeah, I did. - And? How did that go?
结果...  就是车祸现场
It was a... it was a car crash.
我去  我很遗憾  为什么  出了什么事
Oh, shit. I'm sorry. Why? What happened?
我...  我把事情搞砸了  她...
I just, um, I fucked it up, uh, and she's...
听着  她...
Oh, look, she's...
那弗兰克呢
What about Frank?
他...  他和她讲过话吗
Does he, you know, does he ever talk to her?
没有  他是唱红脸的
Uh, no, he's the good cop.
你给自己放过假吗
You ever give yourself a break?
我意思是  你有给过自己时间吗
I mean, do you ever just get to take time for yourself?
你是要告诉我  我看着精疲力尽吗
Are you about to tell me I look exhausted?
不  不
No. No.
但看起来你好像背负着很多沉重的东西
But it seems like you're carrying a lot of heavy stuff,
我很好奇是否有人
and I, you know, I wonder if anybody
会为你做点什么
ever does anything for you.
听着...
Listen...
周六是我生日  我并非想要个礼物
Saturday is my birthday. Not that I expect a gift,
但要不让我带你出去吧
but why don't you let me take you out?
我们要去哪儿
Where are we goin'?
我还不确定  但我会想出主意的
I don't know, but I will figure it out,
7点钟我去接你时
and I will surprise you when I pick you up
会给你惊喜
at seven o'clock.
有天晚上有人给我打了电话
So, someone called me the other night,
跟我说凯蒂还活着
telling me that Katie was alive
并且知道她人在哪里
and that they knew where she was.
天啊  他们怎么说的
Oh, my God. Well, what did they say?
如果我想知道她在哪里的话
If I wanted to find out where,
我就得付给他五千块
I'd have to give 'em five thousand dollars.
这是骗人的  这事我听着不太对
Okay. Well, that's a scam. That is-- I don't like that.
你得去告诉梅尔
You need to tell Mare about that.
你说得对  我确实应该
Yeah, you're right. I should.
不过梅尔现在不上班了
Mare's not working anymore, though.
什么
What?
我在凯马特遇到简・凯利了
Yeah. I ran into Jan Kelly at Kmart.
她情绪明显有点失控
Apparently, she had some sort of breakdown.
家里的事  还有她离婚的事等等
You know, her family stuff, her divorce.
凯文
Kevin.
我也说不好
I don't know.
我觉得可能也有我的原因
I feel like I might've played a part in all of that.
不  你做了所有母亲都会做的事
No. You did exactly...  what any mother would do.
真的
You did.
-道恩  -你好  弗雷迪
- Hey, Dawn. - Hiya, Freddie.
你没告诉我他又回这边住了
You didn't tell me he was back living here.
他过去几天都住在地下室
Yeah. He's been living in the basement the past few days.
他周五吸毒过量了
He overdosed on Friday.
就在迪桑托的熟食店门口
Right in front of DeSanto's Deli.
警察带着纳洛酮来了
Police showed up with Narcan
真的是把他从鬼门关拉了回来
and literally brought him back from the dead.
天啊  你怎么不告诉我
Jesus. Why didn't you tell me?
你的事还不够多吗
With everything you've got going on? No.
没什么事  他挺好的
It's fine. It's fine. He's fine.
贝丝  行了
Bethy, come on.
好吧  特伦斯没有...
Okay. Terrence does not...
我想他只是...
I think he's just...
这整件事情正在毁掉我们的婚姻
This whole thing is ruining our marriage.
我也不知道  他是我弟弟
I don't know, like-- I just-- He's my brother,
如果他在我身边的话
and I feel like if he's here with me,
我就知道他没有飘荡在外
then I know that he's not just out there.
没事  我很好  抱歉
It's okay. I'm fine. I'm sorry.
我现在不想谈这个
I'm not gonna do this right now.
晚饭好了
Dinner's ready.
这是我们第一次一起过夜
It's our first sleepover together.
一  二  三  看
One, two, three, ta-da!
你觉得怎么样  还不错  对吧
What do you think? It's not bad, right?
-嗯  -就目前来说
- Right. - For now?
想去看看你的床吗
Wanna go check out your bed?
-想  -去吧
- Yeah. - Come on.
我还拿来了你的投影仪  你可以看星星
I even got you your projector. For your stars.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
我真高兴你能过来
I'm so happy you're here.
饿吗
Hey, you hungry?
-饿  -想吃披萨吗
- Yeah. - You wanna get some pizza?
披萨披萨披萨
Pizza, pizza, pizza.
等等  你还是喜欢披萨的  对吧
So, wait, you still like pizza, right?
-对  -好
- Right. - Right.
来  瞧瞧
Come on, let's see.
昨天是DJ的一岁生日
It was DJ's first birthday yesterday, and...
我  我在翻看自己的旧日记
I-- I was going through my old journals,
重读着去年里写下的东西
just re-reading entries over the past year, and...
出生日期  2018年11月10日
艾琳・麦克梅纳明
艾琳
日记
Instagram
我总是觉得好累好累
I'm just so tired and exhausted all the time, and...
有些晚上  我真心觉得
It's just like, some nights I, like, seriously feel
自己是个糟糕的妈妈
like a terrible mother.
我希望他有一个美好的人生
I want him to have a great life,
我也在努力为他创造条件
and I'm trying to give that to him.
我真的好想好想给他一切
I just want so bad to give him everything...
凯文  凯文  开门
Kevin! Kevin, open the door.
我就想看看你有没有钱
I just wanna see if you have any money!
你跟我说你没钱  我就想看看
You told me you didn't, so I wanna see
-你是不是在撒谎  -把门打开  妈的
- if you're a liar or not. - Open this door, goddamnit!
你休想用我的钱买毒品
You're not buying drugs with my money!
瞧瞧这个
Look at that!
你他妈果然在撒谎  跟我猜的一样
You're a fucking liar, just like I thought you were.
该死
Fuck!
把门锁起来  锁起来
Lock it! Lock it! Lock it, lock it, lock it.
你什么他妈毛病
What the fuck is your problem?
-把钱包给我  -凯莉  快跑
- Fucking give me my purse! - Go! Carrie, run!
想都别想...
And don't think about getting--
-不许动他  -凯文  住手
- Don't fucking touch him! - Kevin, stop!
你他妈什么毛病
What the fuck is wrong with you?
求你了  住手吧  凯文  住手
Please, stop it, Kevin. Stop it, Kevin!
我他妈恨死你了  恨死你了
I fucking hate you! Fucking hate you.
该死的蠢婊子
You stupid fucking bitch.
他睡不着  说想他的乌龟了
He, uh, couldn't sleep. Said he missed his turtle.
-嘿  你还好吗  -嗯
- Hey. Hi. You okay? - Yeah.
-感觉都还好  -嗯
- You feel okay? - Yeah.
好  那上去睡觉吧  好吗  乖
Okay. Well, go on up to bed, okay? Good boy.
-谢了  -我知道是你干的
- Thanks. - I know it was you.
那些毒品
The drugs.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
知道吗  我在很努力振作起来
You know, I'm trying really hard to get my life together.
所以住手吧
So stop.
住手吧
Just stop.
妈妈  妈妈
Mom. Mom!
妈妈
Mom!
求求你
Please!
我讨厌寒冷
I hate the cold.
真的很讨厌
Like, I seriously hate it.
搞笑的是  我以前甚至不觉得有什么区别
It's funny, I didn't even know there was any different
直到大约十岁的时候去了迪士尼乐园
till I went down to Disney World when I was, like, ten.
那里让我觉得  "哇
And it was like, "Wow.
真的有地方永远不会变冷啊"  你懂吗
There are actual places that never get cold," You know?
我和妹妹  我们坐那个太空山飞车
My sister and I, we must've done that Space Mountain ride...
坐了得有十来次
...like, ten times.
我们会上去玩  然后下来  重新排队
We'd just go on, get off, get back in line.
上去玩  下来  重新排队
Go on, get off, get back in line.
我爸爸说
My dad was like,
"我花了那么多钱不是为了让你们姐妹俩
"I didn't pay all this friggin' money for you girls
只玩一个项目的  去玩点别的"
to go on one ride. Do something else."
他当时真的很生气
He was seriously pissed about it.
你是第一次找小姐吗
This your first time doing this?
我们最后一次看见米西已经是三天前了
Uh, it's been three days since we last saw Missy.
她在周四晚上七点左右离家
She left home Thursday night around 7:00,
从那以后我们就再没有她的消息了
and we haven't heard from her since then.
如果有人知道任何相关信息
And, uh, we're just asking anyone who knows anything
我们恳请您联系警方
to please come forward...
帮助米西回家
and bring her home.
本地新闻九台设立了一条举报热线
Local News Nine has set up a tip line
欢迎所有知情人士来电提供
for anyone with information
米西・赛格和凯蒂・贝里失踪的相关信息
about the disappearance of Missy Sager or Katie Bailey.
如果您有任何...
If you have any--
-说不定是个连环杀手干的  -老天  妈
- Maybe it's a serial killer. - Christ, Mom.
这已经是第三个姑娘了  梅尔
Well, I mean, it is the third girl, Mare.
我就说说
Just saying.
-梅尔  你能...  -别说了  妈  别说了
- Mare, will you-- - Don't say it, Mom. Just don't.
别说什么
Don't say what?
别试图劝我不要出门
Don't try and stop me from going out
-履行我的职责  好吗  -梅尔
- and doing my job, okay? - Mare.
在你说这是个坏主意之前
Before you tell me this is a bad idea,
我有听过任何你跟我讲的话吗
have I ever listened to a thing you told me?
我只是想让你走之前
I just wanted you to get the popcorn
去微波炉把爆米花拿出来
out of the microwave before you leave.
好烫
Hot.
我在五金店的时候碰见了苏珊・福斯特
I ran into Susan Foster at the hardware store.
我们好几个月没碰面了
We hadn't seen each other in a few months.
她和我说她读了那篇关于你的文章
She was telling me that she read the article about you.
所以呢
Yeah?
她的长女现在住在东城
Her oldest daughter lives over in Easttown now.
然后我告诉她说你刚被派遣
And I told her that you had just been sent in
去协助一个案子  在克里顿小溪
to help out on the case of that poor girl
发现的一个可怜女孩尸体
that they found at Creedham Creek.
她女儿觉得这事挺好的
Her daughter thought that was a good thing.
显然去年也有一个女孩失踪了
Apparently, there was another missing girl last year.
-凯蒂・贝里  -没错
- Katie Bailey. - Right.
而且所有人对警局处理案件的方式
And everyone's up in arms
都非常不满
over how the police are handling that case.
我觉得他们不了解那个案件多复杂
I don't think they understand how hard of a case that was.
梅尔是个好警探
Mare's a good detective.
他们刚解雇的是梅尔吗
Is Mare the one they just let go?
听起来似乎她力不从心
Well, it sounds like she was maybe in over her head.
他们很幸运能有你帮助
They're lucky they have you.
保佑我们吧  我们的上帝...
Bless us, O Lord...
感谢我们即将从基督我主那里...
And these thy gifts which we're about to receive...
得来的慷慨的赐予
from thy bounty through Christ our Lord.
阿门
Amen.
-你在这做什么呢  -看见那些新闻了
- What are you doing here? - Saw the news.
好吧  进来吧  请进  请进
Right. Uh, come in, come in, come in.
妈  这是梅尔   我的搭档梅尔
Mom, this is my Mare-- my partner, Mare,
-梅尔・希安警探  -这是我妈  朱迪
- Detective Mare Sheehan. - This is my mom, Judy.
你好
Hello.
嗨  梅尔  我们刚还谈到你了
Hi, Mare. We were just talking about you.
你饿吗  我们做了好多吃的
Are you hungry? We made plenty.
不  我...我不饿  谢谢你
No, I'm-- I'm good, thank you.
-来瓶啤酒吗  -可以
- Want a beer? - Sure.
好的  谢谢了
Great. Thank you.
好吧  米西・赛格
Okay. Missy Sager,
以太阳谷高中全班第一名的成绩毕业
graduated top of her class from Sun Valley.
体操  曲棍球  学生会
Gymnastics, field hockey, student council.
她被库兹敦大学的护理专业录取
She enrolled in the nursing program at Kutztown University.
大一那年  她过马路时
Freshman year, she's crossing the street,
一个老妇人闯红灯撞了她  导致髋部骨折
an old lady runs a stop sign and hits her. Fractures her hip.
之后  她奥施康定上瘾  接着吗啡
Soon after, she starts on Oxy, then morphine.
剩下的故事你都知道了
You know the rest of the story.
她的手机在周五凌晨两点23分关机
Her phone was shut off at 2:23 a.M. Friday.
社交媒体账号也毫无消息
Social media accounts all went dark as well.
自此她父母  姐姐  朋友都没她消息了
No contact with her mom, dad, sister, friends since.
豪瑟不觉得这些案件是相关的
Hauser doesn't think these cases are related.
米西・赛格和凯蒂・贝里的案件可能有联系
Missy Sager and Katie Bailey maybe,
但艾琳不是
but not Erin.
豪瑟是来替我的吗
Hauser my replacement?
在警校的时候他是我们的教官
He was our PT instructor at the academy.
我们六个人在他的后车厢里
As a graduation gift,
拉了泡屎作为毕业礼物
all six of us took a shit in his trunk.
那你怎么想的
So, come on. What do you think?
我觉得她们的生活习惯都太不相同了
I think their lifestyles are too different.
凯蒂和米西是瘾君子
Katie and Missy were drug abusers
为了吸毒她们都以卖淫为生
who had turned to prostitution to support their habit.
两人也都有侧门账号
Both had active Sidedoor accounts.
目前没有证据证明
There's no evidence to suggest
艾琳也是妓女
that Erin was involved in prostitution.
没有证据  但是她有可能是
No evidence. But she could have been.
她手机或电脑什么都没发现
Nothing turned up on her phone or computer.
没有帖子  照片  或者邮件
No postings, pictures, or e-mails.
我们知道她儿子耳朵的手术需要钱
We know she needed the money for her son's ear surgery.
耳鼻喉科室告诉我她预订了手术
ENT office told me she scheduled it,
又取消了两次
cancelled, twice.
如果你是一个少女
If you're a teenage girl,
家里有孩子  爸爸又是肯尼那样的人
baby at home and a dad like Kenny,
你不会用这样的照片在你电脑上
you're not gonna open an account on Sidedoor
注册一个侧门账号
with pictures like this on your own computer.
相信我  青春期少女相当狡猾
Trust me, teenage girls are fucking sneaky.
你想跟我说下你被停职的真正原因吗
Wanna tell me the real reason they put you on leave?
以后吧   如果你不介意的话
One day. Right now, I just wanna drink these beers
现在我只想喝点啤酒  聊聊怎么找寻这些少女
and talk about finding these girls, if that's okay.
所以我们想知道的是
So, what we're trying to figure out
为什么艾琳会跟迪伦撒谎说他是孩子爸爸
is why Erin would lie to Dylan about him being the father?
为什么不直接告诉他真相
Why not just tell him the truth?
因为她一直说他的父母对她很好
Because she always said how nice his parents were to her.
他们人有多好
How they were good people.
她希望DJ生活中能一直
She liked the idea of DJ always having
拥有这种爱  明白吗
that kind of love in his life, you know?
她有说过需要钱给DJ做耳朵手术吗
Did she talk about needing money for ear surgery for DJ?
只说过她想让迪伦付这个钱
Just that she wanted Dylan to pay for it.
但他一直跟她说他没钱
But he kept telling her he didn't have the money.
那她说过如果迪伦付不起的话
Did she say how she would get it
她要怎么筹钱吗
if Dylan couldn't pay for it?
杰茜
Jess.
我明白你想保护你的朋友  好吗
I understand you wanna protect your friend, all right?
这非常令人佩服
That's admirable.
但艾琳已经不在了  亲爱的
But Erin's gone, sweetie.
所以你继续保持沉默  唯一得益的
So the only person you're helping by keeping silent
是那个杀了她的人
is the person who killed her.
这个人可能还杀了其他两个女生
Same person who might've killed two more girls.
杰茜
Jess.
她和你说过她打算
Did she tell you how she was planning
怎么搞到耳朵手术的钱吗
on getting the money for that ear surgery?
侧门陪伴服务
贾思敏
她叫我帮她创建一个账号
She asked me to create an account for her.
她不想在家里创建
She didn't wanna make one at home
因为她不想她爸爸发现
'cause she didn't want her dad to find out.
那些照片是你拍的吗  亲爱的
Did you take those pictures, sweetie?
没事
It's okay.
可是  她只打算做一段时间的
But... she was only gonna do it for a little while
直到她存够手术钱
until she saved up enough money for the surgery.
做什么  跟男人做爱吗
Do what? Have sex with men?
是的  但她从没有过
Well, yeah. But she never did.
没有  她跟我说
No, she told me that
她实在做不到
she couldn't bring herself to do it, you know.
杰茜
Jess.
这很重要
It's really important.
你确定她一次都没有出去
Are you sure she never once went out
跟那些给她发信息的男人
and met up with just, like, even one of those guys
-见面过吗  -没有  我确定
- who messaged her? - No, I'm sure.
好的  好的
Okay. All right.
你有账号密码吗
Do you have the login and password?
-该死  -怎么了
- Shit. - What's the matter?
我忘拿手机了  等我一下
I left my phone. Give me a sec.
那个  有件事我忘了问
Hey, just, uh-- I had something I forgot to ask.
好的  杰茜
Sure. Jess?
杰茜  你知道她日记放哪里吗
Jess, do you know where she kept her journals?
她房间角落里有个化妆台
Uh, there's a dresser in-- in the corner of her room.
她把日记放在最下面两个抽屉之间
And she keeps them in between the two bottom drawers.
好的  谢谢  谢谢
Okay. Thanks. Thanks.
申请去侧门的搜查令
Get a search warrant over to Sidedoor
索要所有给艾琳账户发送过消息的用户名
with every username that messaged Erin's account.
他们会跟你说需要五个工作日
They'll tell you five business days.
你说你明早前就要
Tell them you need it by tomorrow morning.
-遵命  女士  -抱歉  老习惯
- Yes, ma'am. - Sorry. Old habits.
你周六晚上有什么计划
What are you doing Saturday night?
这周六  我
Uh, this Saturday, I, uh...
要给一个朋友过生
...have a friend's birthday.
好的
Okay.
怎么了
Why?
就是  我一个朋友在肯尼特广场
No, just, uh... A buddy of mine just opened a restaurant
开了家餐厅  我一直
in Kennett Square, and I've been meaning
打算去尝尝
to check it out for a while now, you know.
你是想叫我约会吗  扎博尔
Are you asking me on a date, Zabel?
如果答案是肯定的就算是
I'm only asking if the answer is yes.
-你有空吗  -嗯  进来吧
- You have a minute? - Yeah, come in.
《论坛报》的一个记者刚打来
A reporter from the Tribune just called.
他问我关于你调到
He questioned me, uh, about the circumstances
圣迈克尔教区的背景
of your transfer here to St. Michael's.
你跟他说了什么
Well? What did you tell him?
跟他说了我所知道的一切
Uh, told him everything I knew.
我在同意调任前
That I spoke with the archdiocese at length
跟大主教管区详细谈过
before agreeing to the transfer.
他会写一篇报道
He's gonna write an article.
我们的教区居民会知道的  马克
Our parishioners are gonna find out, Mark.
我
I...
有义务保护这个教区的成员
am responsible for protecting the members of this parish.
我不知道你想要我说什么  丹
I don't know what else you want me to say, Dan.
我已经跟你说了发生的一切
I already told you everything that happened.
-一切吗  -是的
- Everything? - Yes.
除非你不再相信我
Unless you don't believe me anymore.
当然相信  晚安
Of course. Good night.
晚安
Good night.
我不要  我不要
Not me. Not me!
停下
Stop.
-停下  -这就是那个纪录片吗
- Stop! - Oh, is this the documentary?
-嗯  -笑容很好看
- Yeah. - Good smile.
天啊  凯文看上去很开心
Oh, my God. Kevin looks so happy there.
你们俩以前很亲近
So, you two were pretty close?
有时候  我感觉他是我最好的朋友
Mm. Sometimes, I felt like he was my best friend,
而有时  我又感觉我完全不认识他
and other times, I felt like I didn't know him at all.
你有想好你想说什么了吗
Mm. Have you figured out what you wanna say yet?
我觉得我是想试图明白他为什么那么做
I think it's my attempt to try and understand why he did it.
进展不是很顺利
It's not going very well.
你们是怎么挺过来的  太难了
How did you all get through that? Damn.
我们没有  我们分崩离析了
We didn't. We fell apart.
所以你才想在这上大学吗
Is that why you wanna stick around here for college?
你害怕如果你离开
You're afraid if you leave,
你们又会散架
everything will fall apart again?
别为别人而活  雪芳
Don't live your life for anyone else, Siobhan.
我现在有进步了
Well, I'm making a little progress.
是吗
Yeah?
我一直想跟年纪大点的女人交往
I always wanted to date an older woman, so...
不  狗屁
Well, actually, no, that's bullshit.
我先约你的
I asked you out first.
-海伦  -嗨
- Hi, Helen. - Hi.
-雪芳在家吗  -不  她出去了
- Um, is Siobhan home? - Oh, no, she went out.
我能进去吗
Could I come in for a sec?
当然  进来吧
Yeah, sure. Sure, yeah, come on in.
我
So, i--
我估计你听说了她和我分手的消息了
I guess you heard the news that she broke up with me?
没事的  亲爱的
It's all right, hon.
我只是不
I just don't--
我不想失去她  她就像是
I don't wanna lose her, you know? She's like...
我这操蛋生活里唯一的好事
...the one good thing I have in my shitty fucking life.
她是个很好的人  雪芳
She's a very good person, Siobhan.
她特别棒
Yeah, she's fucking amazing.
抱歉  她
Sorry, she's--
她真的很棒  我只是
Yeah, she's, like, really amazing, and I just--
我只是想过来  让她知道这点
Yeah, I think I just wanted to come here and let her know that.
好的  她知道你会来吗
okay. Uh, is she expecting you?
嗯
Yeah, um...
她发短信说她在外面购物
Yeah, she just texted saying she was just out shopping
过几分钟回家
and she'd be home in a few minutes.
好的  德鲁在他房间睡觉
Okay, well, uh, Drew's asleep in his room,
你去地下室等吧
so, um, why don't you wait in the basement?
左边
Uh, on the left.
抱歉
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
我
I--
-我过得很开心  -我也是
- I had a really nice time. - Me, too.
我们进去吧
Let's go inside.
贝卡
Becca?
贝卡  贝卡  等等  贝卡
Becca. Becca! Wait, Becca!
不  不  不
No, no, no, no, no.
天  对不起
God. I'm so sorry!
我的天  外婆  外婆  你还好吗
Oh, my God. Gran? Gran? Gran, are you okay?
你能叫救护车吗  拜托
Can you-- can you call an ambulance, please?
你能听到我吗  外婆
Can you hear me, Gran?
我的天  天啊  老天啊
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Jesus fucking Christ.
搞什么
What the hell?
-妈  -老天
- Mom! - Jesus.
-就这点伤吗  -就这点伤吗
- Is that it? - Is that it?
抱歉  我不是那意思
Well, just-- Sorry, no.
只是雪芳在电话里的语气
It's just the way Siobhan sounded on the phone,
我以为很严重
I assumed it'd be a lot worse.
抱歉我没有伤得更重
Well, I'm sorry I'm not more maimed for you.
让她下来  艾迪
Come on, get her out of this thing, Eddie.
她就是额头上划伤了
She's got a papercut on her forehead.
她晕头转向了  梅尔  不知道现在是哪年
She's disoriented, Mare. Didn't know what year it was.
这不稀奇了
Well, that's, you know, nothing's new there.
我们要带她去里德尔医院做检查
We're gonna take her to Riddle to have her evaluated.
-你想陪她去吗  -不知道  当然
- You wanna ride with her? - Uh, I don't know. Sure.
妈  你要我陪你去吗
Mom, you want me to ride with you?
嗯
Yeah.
好
Okay.
妈  等等
Mom, wait!
外婆叫我把她的包拿来
Gran's asked for her purse.
-好  -嗯
- Okay. - Yeah.
-你把车开走  -好
- You move the car, sweetie. - Uh, yeah.
-那是谁  -就是个朋友
- Who is that? - Um, just-- just, uh, a friend.
你好  朋友
Hi, friend.
-我晚点给你打电话  -嗯
- I'll call you later. - Yeah.
-好的  -好了
- All right. - Okay.
那女人是谁  妈
Who was that woman? Mom.
跟雪芳在一起的那女人是谁
Who was that woman with, uh, Siobhan?
那是  是贝卡
It was-- it was Becca.
不  那不是贝卡
No, that was not Becca.
喂
Hello?
凯蒂女儿的中间名是格蕾丝
Katie's daughter's middle name is Grace.
她脚踝上文了她的生日
She has a tattoo of her birthday on her ankle.
你现在信我了吗  道恩
Do you believe me now, Dawn?
-信  -很好
- Yes. - Good.
明晚前准备好五千块
Five thousand dollars by tomorrow night.
我会打电话告诉你把钱放哪  道恩
I'll call you with instructions where to drop the money, Dawn.
如果你报警
And if you go to the police,
你将只会找到凯蒂的骨头
all you're ever gonna find of Katie are her bones.
你看见过我吗  凯蒂・贝里
凯蒂・贝里
下落不明
亲爱的艾琳
爱你的妈妈
又一个女孩失踪让社区里的人惶惶不安
News of another missing girl has stoked fear in a community
第三个失踪女孩
他们还沉浸在艾琳・麦克梅纳明的谋杀
already reeling from the murder of Erin McMenamin
以及凯蒂・贝里的失踪所带来的悲痛中
and the disappearance of Katie Bailey.
23岁的米西・赛格
Twenty-three-year-old Missy Sager,
曾是太阳谷高中一位前途光明的毕业生
once a promising young graduate of Sun Valley High,
她的生活在近些年里急转直下
whose life has taken a dark turn in recent years,
周四晚出门后就再未归来
left home on Thursday night and has not returned since.
他们现在又在说什么
What are they saying now?
跟凯蒂・贝里的失踪或者...的死亡有关
...connected to the disappearance of Katie Bailey, or the death...
人人都得小心  伙计
Just everybody needs to be careful, bud.
警方称...
Now police are saying...
我不想要你和莫伊拉
I don't want you and Moira walking home
第三个失踪女孩
再从学校走路回家了  好吗
from school anymore, okay?
我或者你们爸爸会来接你们
Either me or Dad will pick you up.
好
Okay.
或者有任何跟此案相关的信息
...or has any information regarding the case,
请立刻联系他们
to please contact them immediately.
当局跟我们说他们要加大镇区的
Authorities have told us that they are going to increase
巡逻警力
patrols in the township.
在他先前的新闻发布会上
In his press conference earlier,
东城警局局长卡特没有说
Easttown Police Chief Carter didn't go as far as to say
当地居民生活在恐惧之中
三起案子之间有关联
that all three cases were linked,
但他仍然鼓励居民保持警惕
but he is still encouraging residents to be vigilant
防止再次发生悲剧
in an effort to prevent yet another tragedy.
你还好吗
You all right?
我得来看看你  医生的嘱咐
I'm supposed to check on you. Doctor's orders.
确保你没有变得更糟  有吗
Make sure you're not getting any worse. Are you?
跟平时没差
I don't feel any worse then I usually do.
那就好
Good enough for me.
你周六晚有空照看德鲁吗
Oh, are you around Saturday night to watch Drew?
应该有  怎么了
Should be. Why?
-我有约会  -那个作家吗
- Uh, I have a date. - The writer?
还不知道  晚安
I don't know yet. Night.
这是什么意思
What's that mean?
好了  保姆来了
All right. The babysitter is here.
谢谢帮忙  贝丝
Well, thanks for helping me out, Bethy.
没什么  我很乐意  我还买了披萨
Any time. Any time. I even bought pizza
-以防你饿了  肯齐  -有披萨吃呢  肯齐
- in case you're hungry, Kenz. - Ooh, pizza, Kenz.
我午夜下班  贝丝  谢谢
My shift ends at midnight, Beth. Thank you.
-听话哦  肯齐  -马上回来  亲爱的
- Be good, Kenzie. - Be right back, honey.
喂
Hello?
上收费公路
Get on the turnpike.
走903号国道出口
Take the State Road 903 exit.
在哈兰路左转
Make a left at Harlan Road.
向西开3英里
Head west for three miles.
你会看到一道木栅栏  标记了房子的边界
You'll see a wooden fence marking the edge of the property.
那有栋房子
There's a home there.
你会在地下室里找到凯蒂
You'll find Katie in the basement.
该死  该死
Shit. Oh, shit.
该死
Shit.
靠
Shit!
操
Fuck!
弗雷迪
Freddie?
抱歉  道恩
Sorry, Dawn.
对不起
Fuckin' sorry.
我叫你睡我床上的
I told you to sleep in my bed.
我试过  可我
Yeah, I tried that, but I--
我的天
Oh, my God.
-天啊  发生了什么  -我没事
- Oh, my God. What happened? - I'm fine.
我在商店外跌倒了
I just took a little spill outside of the store.
我的天  你需要去看医生吗
Oh, my God, we-- Do you need to go see a doctor?
不  不  我没事
No, no, I'm fine.
让我坐一会儿
Just let me sit down for a minute.
你需要
Well, can I get you some--
我去给你拿点水
Let me get you some water or something.
谢谢
Thanks.
都是放疗  我总是晕晕的
It's just the radiation. I feel dizzy all the time.
我都不知道
I didn't know that.
给
Here.
你确定你不需要我带你去医院吗
Are you sure you don't want me to take you to the hospital?
-因为  -贝丝
- 'Cause-- - Bethy...
-我没事  -亲爱的  你看上去不好
- I'm fine. - Honey, you don't look fine.
我没事
I'm fine.
好
Okay.
你有报警跟他们说
Did you ever call the police about that person who--
那个打电话来说知道凯蒂在哪的人吗
who called and said they knew where Katie was?
嗯
Yeah.
他们跟你一个看法
Yeah. They agreed with you.
他们说可能是骗子
And they say it was probably some scammer
想要搞点钱
looking to make some money.
嗯
Yeah.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
没事  没事  我没事  谢谢  贝丝
It's okay. It's okay. I'm okay. Thanks, Bethy.
谢谢
Thank you.
本尼酒馆
不  不  不
No! No! No!
不
No!
没人能听到你
No one can hear you in here.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是凯蒂  凯蒂・贝里
I'm Katie. Katie Bailey.